<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Submission Aplikasi Android Sederhana</string>
    <string name="players_name">Nama Pemain</string>
    <string name="description">Deskripsi</string>
    <string name="position">Posisi</string>
    <string name="birthdate">Tanggal Lahir</string>

    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>David De Gea</item>
        <item>Luke Shaw</item>
        <item>Lisandro Martínez</item>
        <item>Raphaël Varane</item>
        <item>Diogo Dalot</item>
        <item>Casemiro</item>
        <item>Christian Eriksen</item>
        <item>Bruno Fernandes</item>
        <item>Jadon Sancho</item>
        <item>Antony</item>
        <item>Marcus Rashford</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>David de Gea Quintana is a Spanish professional footballer who plays as a goalkeeper for Premier League club Manchester United and the Spain national team. He is widely regarded as one of the best goalkeepers in the world.</item>
        <item>Luke Paul Hoare Shaw is an English professional footballer who plays as a left-back or centre-back for Premier League club Manchester United and the England national team.</item>
        <item>Lisandro Martínez, also known as Licha Martínez, is an Argentine professional footballer who plays primarily as a centre-back for Premier League club Manchester United and the Argentina national team. Martínez is nicknamed "the Butcher of Amsterdam" due to his aggressive style of defending.</item>
        <item>Raphaël Xavier Varane is a French professional footballer who plays as a centre-back for Premier League club Manchester United. Considered as one of the best defenders of his generation, Varane is known for his defensive prowess and speed.</item>
        <item>José Diogo Dalot Teixeira is a Portuguese professional footballer who plays as a right-back for Premier League club Manchester United and the Portugal national team. Dalot is a product of the Porto youth system</item>
        <item>Carlos Henrique Casimiro, known as Casemiro, is a Brazilian professional footballer who plays as a defensive midfielder for Premier League club Manchester United and the Brazil national team. He is regarded as one of the best defensive midfielders of his generation.</item>
        <item>Christian Dannemann Eriksen is a Danish professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Premier League club Manchester United and the Denmark national team. He is renowned for his vision, technique, passing, and free kick ability.</item>
        <item>Bruno Miguel Borges Fernandes is a Portuguese professional footballer who plays as an attacking midfielder for Premier League club Manchester United and the Portugal national team. He is known for his goalscoring, playmaking, leadership, penalty taking, and work rate.</item>
        <item>Jadon Malik Sancho is an English professional footballer who plays as a winger for Premier League club Manchester United and the England national team. Considered one of the best young players in the world, he is known for his trickery, game intelligence and use of feints in one-on-one situations.</item>
        <item>Antony Matheus dos Santos, simply known as Antony, is a Brazilian professional footballer who plays as a winger for Premier League club Manchester United and the Brazil national team. Antony graduated from the São Paulo academy and made his senior debut for the club in 2018.</item>
        <item>Marcus Rashford MBE is an English professional footballer who plays as a forward for Premier League club Manchester United and the England national team. Considered one of the best forwards in the world, he is known for his attacking, dribbling, composure, and athleticism.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_position">
        <item>Goalkeeper</item>
        <item>Defender</item>
        <item>Defender</item>
        <item>Defender</item>
        <item>Defender</item>
        <item>Midfielder</item>
        <item>Midfielder</item>
        <item>Midfielder</item>
        <item>Forward</item>
        <item>Forward</item>
        <item>Forward</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_birth">
        <item>Born : November 7, 1990 (age 32 years) </item>
        <item>Born : July 12, 1995 (age 27 years) </item>
        <item>Born : January 18, 1998 (age 25 years)</item>
        <item>Born : April 25, 1993 (age 29 years)</item>
        <item>Born : March 18, 1999 (age 23 years)</item>
        <item>Born : February 23, 1992 (age 31 years)</item>
        <item>February 14, 1992 (age 31 years)</item>
        <item>September 8, 1994 (age 28 years)</item>
        <item>March 25, 2000 (age 22 years)</item>
        <item>February 24, 2000 (age 23 years)</item>
        <item>October 31, 1997 (age 25 years)</item>

    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_photo">
        <item>@drawable/degea</item>
        <item>@drawable/shaw</item>
        <item>@drawable/licha</item>
        <item>@drawable/varane</item>
        <item>@drawable/dalot</item>
        <item>@drawable/casemiro</item>
        <item>@drawable/eriksen</item>
        <item>@drawable/bruno</item>
        <item>@drawable/sancho</item>
        <item>@drawable/antony</item>
        <item>@drawable/rashy</item>

    </integer-array>
</resources>